So you've been coding in Python for over
10 years now. How different do you view
the software engineering space now that
we have all these AI tools?
>> I don't write a single line of code
anymore. Not a single. So everything
goes through codecs or through cloud
code. Think about any skill you would
learn. You're not going to start at the
elite level. But right now we all start
with these same really great tools that
can help us produce code.
>> If you had to put a number to it, how
much faster do you think you're able to
move now? Well, compared to when I was
just starting out, probably 100x, you
can build useful stuff with one prompt.
Heck, you can even build entire software
products that you could sell even if you
have a limited technical background.
>> Do you have any examples of maybe
landmines that you've stepped on when
trying to scale something,
>> the stakes get bigger and bigger and
bigger as you start to build software
that's used by more and more people,
there are certain obligations when it
comes to data privacy and protection,
security breach. That's one thing that
you cannot take back. Once those emails
and that personal data is leaked, you
can't go back.
>> If I was starting today with no
technical experience, I would be most
excited about this.
>> All right, Dave. So, you've been coding
in Python for over 10 years now. Your
team has delivered 50 plus AI solutions
with Glido. You are shipping new
features and updates like every week. I
just want to know how different do you
view the software engineering space now
that we have all these AI tools.
>> Oh man, what a question to kick this off
with. Well, obviously it's completely
different. It's completely different.
What happened over the past three years
and especially what happened in the last
year is just wild. It's just crazy in
terms of what we can do right now. And
we're all experiencing this, right?
We're all using these tools. We're all
producing lots of code. We're building.
And so first of all, it's like really
exciting. So if you ask me like what is
mainly different from when I started out
back in 2013, so like over 10 years ago
already, well, first of all, coding was
really freaking hard [laughter]
and learn and learning and learning to
code as well. And you would just spend
so much time working on this tidy little
program, looking up Stack Overflow, and
then trying to make stuff work, right?
So you could build small little things
and then if you worked on something long
enough you could build something useful
maybe right now fast forward in the
world that we live in today you can
build useful stuff with one prompt and
we all know that we see it on your
channel like every week just one prompt
and you you can build stuff. So what
that then also means is that we can now
just think bigger as developers, as
builders, and we can now do stuff and
build stuff that just wasn't realistic
or possible a couple of years ago. So
that means we can build automations for
yourself, for personal productivity, for
your company, inside the company, for
clients. Heck, you can even build entire
software products that you could sell
even if you have limited a limited
technical background. That's now all
possible and it's getting faster every
week.
>> If you had to put a number to it, how
much faster do you think you're able to
move now?
>> Well, compared to when I was just
starting out, probably 100x. Well,
that's not fair because I was a complete
noob. But let's say let's [laughter] do
a little bit more of a of a realistic
take. Let's say we go back to 2022.
At that time, I was already working as a
freelance data scientist, data analyst
for like two or three years at that
point. So, I was professionally writing
code mostly Python code almost every day
for already three years.
>> Okay. If I look at that point right now
and see like how much I could ship and
produce and do and all of that compared
to what I can do right now, I would I
would still put it like a solid 10x like
a solid 10x of actual useful like
production ready code that you can ship
and on some projects is maybe even more
because I can now also work on projects
and work with languages that before were
just not possible. So I come from a
Python background, data scientist, later
AI engineering. So I used to make
backend systems. But if you were to ask
me to build like a a shiny like front
end or dashboard, I have like I have
never written a single line of
JavaScript like actually in my life
pretty much. I only started to pick that
up once the coding agents were there. I
was like, "Yeah, like let's just try
it." Right? So that is I think a
distinction like like a solid 10x on on
the work that I already did
professionally but like probably even
more than that on other like
possibilities that I just couldn't do
before.
>> Gotcha. So before kind of preai
engineers would kind of typically
specialize in either like more of the
back end at a very high level like a
back end or a front end and it was a
very different way you thought about
writing that code.
>> Oh yeah for sure. And you of course you
have full stack engineers as well. But
then even with full stack it would it
was probably focused on like specific
languages and you know you back then you
also had these like 10x engineers right
like the the old legends of these and
you have you had these like just crazy
developers that could do it all but
generally speaking mostly people would
either do back end front end security
infrastructure they would have like one
or two languages that they're
comfortable with and that is now um that
that is now completely like flipped on
its head.
>> So now instead of really having to
specialize, everyone that's building can
sort of be a jack of all trades there,
more of a generalist and and feel
confident that they are kind of able to
write high quality code in maybe some of
the areas that they weren't super
proficient in beforehand.
>> Yes, for sure. And I also would highly
recommend
everyone to try and do that because why
is that the case? If you don't if you
stick to specialization where of course
like there there's always value in
specialization right so maybe people
watching if you're working in enterprise
let's say you're working for meta or
Google or whatever and you're part of
like a highly specialized team
>> you need to be top 1% of what you're
doing right you need to be a hyper
specialist [clears throat]
>> but let's be real most people don't work
in the top 1% at mad at Google and all
of that most of us are like we're
building we like to build stuff and
there you can better nowadays be a
generalist because if you specialize
means you focus on one part of the
project let's say means you also need
other people to deliver something end to
end to ship something and now your AI
agents can move way faster than you can
communicate and keep can keep up with
teammates so if you cannot work across
the entire stack you are quite quickly
going to hit a bottleneck where your
agent is all already ready, right? It's
ready to ship. It's ready to work on the
next part. But if for example, I don't
know, there is not an integration with
the front end because you only do back
end or um you don't know how to work
with the databases and adjust your back
end to the database, right? there is a
dependency and that creates problems and
I've seen really in the first of all the
projects that I've worked on the teams
that I've worked with but also now what
we do in glido and how we build glido
that we have very of course still we
have separate roles and responsibilities
and we have more people but we give
people complete ownership on a
particular aspect of the product where
they can really ship from something from
like start to finish on their own
without needing someone else other than
like maybe a review from someone in the
process, right? But not like actual work
or code that needs to be developed. So I
think being a generalist is the best way
to go. It's now possible. So you can
just get better at um engineering, learn
engineering principles and then which
language or framework you apply that to
uh starts to matter less and less.
>> Real quick guys, I just have to take a
second to tell you about the sponsor of
today's video, Code Rabbit. So, I know
that a lot of you guys are building with
coding agents now. And the code
definitely piles up faster than you can
actually read it because the agent
doesn't just touch one file at a time.
It goes through your routes, your
schemas, your tests, and your config in
a single pass. And then you open the
pull request and GitHub gives you an
alphabetical list of files. So, you're
rebuilding the logic in your own head.
So, Chainstack is Code Rabbit's review
interface for that exact problem. What
it does is it splits the pull request
into cohorts of related work and orders
them by what depends on what. So, it
reads it in the order that it was
actually built. It opens on an overview
page with the summary, the walkthrough,
and what's blocking merge, merge
conflicts, and failing CI checks you can
fix from the page in one click. There's
also a timeline of every change,
approval, and comment. So, you can see
why each decision got made. And the
semantic diff view is the part that I
would probably use the most because when
code gets moved, a normal diff shows it
deleted on one side and added back on
the other, bearing the real change. The
semantic view shows you what actually
changed. And you can ask the agent
questions about the PR right on that
page. So, if you're shipping more agent
code than you can read, there's a free
14-day trial. No credit cards required.
The link is in the description. And huge
thanks to Code Rabbit for sponsoring
this part of the video. Now, let's get
back to it. I hear you. And I think that
I'm really excited for this conversation
because my audience is typically people
that are coming from a nontechnical
background. And it seems like your
audience is like the exact opposite. And
>> one one thing that I hear from my
audience like when you know I'm building
stuff and I always sometimes wonder is
this right? You know cuz the only really
source of truth that I can trust is my
agent and that's not always going to be
the source of truth that you want to
trust.
>> I'm curious you know I want to zoom out
and I want to start from the very
beginning but real quick before we
transition into that. I'm just curious
how did you feel about the whole vibe
coding era like when that term really
started to pop up and you as a software
engineer there was probably so many
alarms going off in your head when
everyone was just picking up these tools
and started you know building apps and
stuff like that.
>> Yeah. So first of all I found it very
exciting because the thing is I was also
very much part of that whole vibe coders
journey even though I have uh experience
as an engineer like I've said I was now
also creating front-end applications
fully custom code websites
>> and I wasn't reading the code and I
couldn't care so like that would also
put me in in a category of like five
coder
>> and even though that I technically know
how to like set up an architecture and
how to secure your applications and all
of that, right? That of course helps and
that adds a little bit of um just extra
experience to it. But I'm very much pro
pro vibe coding. You just need to know
what the stakes are depending on what
you're working on, right? Because
>> if you're building if you're building
your personal website,
>> by all means like vibe away. There's
like zero risk, right? But it it's
always about like risk versus reward
trade-off. So I think it's awesome that
everyone can build right now. I can
build more. Uh that's super fun. Anyone
can build. And then the question is you
just need to start being careful like
once you let other users, other people
use your software and especially when
personal data is involved, right? So
that's that's I think where you need to
draw kind of like a fine line in terms
of like how far can you really just push
things without really understanding
what's going on and just going off of
the looks or like checking whether
something works and diving deeper into
hm let's see if this actually is secure
because now it's not your only your own
data that you're working with but it's
also other people's right so I think
that is um yeah so that is kind of like
my view on the whole vibe coding uh turn
more or trend really that was going on.
>> I hear you. Yeah. I mean it's very cool
because we see all of these stories of
people, you know, from whatever sort of
background that just have this idea and
then they start talking to an AI agent
and they're able to actually run with
it. And we've seen some pretty cool
exits. We've seen people just change
their lives because they've been able to
take their idea and turn it into
something. So, let's actually like kind
of walk through that process a little
bit. If someone has an idea and they
want to sit down this weekend and they
want to start building that out, what
how would you do that? What what sort of
steps and planning do you go through in
order to start building some sort of app
or software?
>> Great question. So, so let let's walk
through this. So,
first of all,
you need to get a rough idea
of how big the thing is that you want to
build.
Because when it comes to building
products and let's focus on software
products uh right now to make it a
little bit simpler right um there's
different level different levels to
things
>> okay
>> so first of all I would say ask yourself
the question is this something is this a
software tool that just you want to use
like because you want to have some type
of tool either something that you're
currently paying for right now that you
don't want to have a subscription for
anymore or just something that doesn't
exist or you want to combine m multiple
tools into one like is it something that
you just want to use. So, so that that's
like one question because another level
could be uh for example, yes, it's for
me, but it's also for example for people
within my company. So, maybe it's like a
team thing, a company thing or maybe
it's something where you say I want to
build something and I want to sell that
to other people. So, I want to have this
as like an AI agency offer maybe, right?
So, I sell it to other companies or I
sell it to other people. Mhm.
>> And that could be partly productized
meaning you build something you package
it and you sell it or it can be partly a
surface right so there's you build
something but then there's a surface
element to it as well right so you help
implement it into businesses this is all
related to for example like AI
automation right as you know no single
automation is ever 100% the same so
there's also an a customization
component to it and then the another
level is do you want to build like a
software product like fully handoff that
people can just jump on a subscription.
They can just go to a website, create an
account, download it, get on a
subscription, and use it. For example,
what we're doing with Glido, right? So,
there's these four different categories
uh that that your ID could fall into.
And why is that important? Because as
you progress up that ladder, I say I
would I would position it as a ladder.
Um it gets more complex and the stakes
are bigger. Again, summarize, if you
just build something for you, you use
it. Stakes are very low. Just just go
and build. Just open cloud code and go
for it.
>> If you use it inside your team, other
people use it. It's still considered
internal, right? But you may already
want to be a little bit more careful
like who's going to use this? What are
what kind of like data is going to be in
this application? Now then if you sell
it to to uh a company there's even like
a legal aspect involved right because
you probably have a contractor's terms
of service there is certain there are
certain obligations when it comes to
data privacy and protection so there's a
bigger risk
>> and then the and the other level is the
like when you actually build the
software product and you let um
consumers use it we have the whole idea
of data privacy and and personal rights
and all of that when it comes to data so
and and probably more people using it.
So just the risk gets bigger. So um
let's pause there for a second because
that that's what I think uh it's good to
start there.
>> Um so was that all clear?
>> Yeah. So it sounds like before you start
building you want to kind of have an
idea of essentially you said how big and
that makes me think like how many how
many people will use this? How many
hands will this touch? And would it be
fair to say that a good way to get
started is you kind of start on that
first rung of the ladder where it's like
I'm going to build this first just so I
can use it. And that's sort of the way
I'm thinking about it. And that doesn't
mean that later if I wanted to have my
team use it, I couldn't scale up the
back end because, you know, it sounds
like as you move up the ladder of
requirements and people, you have to
think about other things like the
architecture a little bit more and the
database and just making sure that it
can handle this stuff, the privacy. But
it's totally fine to start off on that
first rung and then when you need to
move up, you can start to do that,
right? It's not like you choose, okay,
this is going to be a personal tool and
then later, maybe six months later, you
realize you want to scale it up. You're
not like stuck, right? You're always
able to continue to move up the ladder.
>> Yeah, I think that's a that's a very
good clarification because of course you
can always like make the ambition
bigger, right, of the project. And I
think one of the tr uh one thing to
watch out for is for example like
skipping levels and being someone for
example no technical background and
jumping straight into building custom
software and then selling that to people
and letting companies rely on
[clears throat] it. Right? So there you
skipped a couple of steps in terms of
like your homework in order to figure
out okay what does this look like? What
does this mean? What data is flowing
through it? So I think that is a a very
like natural way to progress in there
because you're totally right. So when we
make that a little bit more kind of like
tactical as to what's different right
there is not much different nowadays in
terms of the process it is still even
for my projects like I don't write a
single line of code anymore not a single
so everything goes through nowadays
either through through codeex or through
cloud code or even through grot
depending on kind of like who has the
best models so everything goes through
the coding agents so that's also
interesting like for the audience uh
watching that I think this is the very
first time in history where someone with
zero coding skills and someone who has
been doing this for over a decade use
the exact same tools and the exact same
process which is quite quite wild to
think about it right now just like now
that I'm explaining this I'm just like
making this up but now I think about it
it's actually pretty wild because think
about any skill that you would learn
right if you just start with, I don't
know, playing basketball or anything
like that. You're not going to start at
like the elite level like your exercises
and what you do is going to be way
different, right? But right now, we all
start with these same really really
great tools that can help us produce
code. So the only thing that is like
different is what instructions do you
give it and how do you review the
output, right? And then that's the
skill. That is where like the reps come
in and that's where also the stakes get
bigger and bigger and bigger as you
start to build software that's used by
by more and more people. But I think
that is like very motivating for like
people to watch. Like you have these
tools you can jump on like a $20
subscription. You probably want to get
to like $100 and $200 otherwise you know
you run out.
>> You'd be sitting there all week like man
when is this reset coming? You probably
want a little bit more, but like that
for most for most people that is within
reach and from that you can start you
can start building and you can start to
build really really cool things and
>> yeah start building with something that
you would use that you think is cool and
then start to make it make it better and
then over time um and we can we can get
into this deeper if if you want to but
there are like for for for the most part
VIP coding is totally fine. But there is
one aspect of it that is security where
you just cannot afford to make the risks
because let's say even if you build an
application and it's like vibe coded and
the architecture is bad like what's the
worst thing that can happen like people
will use it and at some point like it
will like get a little bit slower or it
will break but you'll notice right
you'll start fixing it. So there's
nothing really like so like and that is
something you'll be aware of because
people start complaining it's like huh
maybe maybe we need to revisit that but
like a security a security breach that's
one thing that you like cannot take back
out sorry we'll fix it in the next
version you know like that's that's out
once once those emails and that personal
data is leaked you can't go back so that
is one aspect that uh we could get into
that if you if you want to but that is I
think the most important thing as you
level up security
>> totally totally and I definitely want to
get into that and I think we'll just
kind of keep working our way up here.
That's why I love the ladder analogy
because you really do have to earn your
way up to the next rung. You can't just
jump from the ground to rung four or
you're probably going to fall and you
you just have to start from the bottom
again. So
>> yeah,
>> it sounds like the first piece is kind
of you figure out how big and you you
think about high level like how big am I
building this and how much risk is there
involved?
>> Yeah,
>> once you kind of have a good idea of
that,
>> what is the next step to start that
building process? What does it look like
for you to sort of map this out in your
head to sort of plan out the
requirements? How does that process
look? Or if that's not the next step,
what is the next step?
>> Yeah. No, that is that is definitely the
next step. So, uh, when you have this
idea and when you want to start just
just building, um, what I've observed
over the, uh, past year, pretty much
one year ago,
everyone was really like pushing
um, spec driven development, the
importance of plans, and you can
probably remember this, right? Um, and
I've just found that as the models get
better and better and better and the
models that we have to right now like
the the planning phase and the
generating the specs becomes like it
becomes less important I found.
>> So what does that mean spec planning?
>> Uh yeah. So spec spec different
development was is uh refers to kind of
like a way of building software where
you first use AI not to produce code but
to produce specs and what are specs?
specifications. So you describe how the
project or the product should work in
natural language. So you and and you
could and you would use AI for this. So
you would pretty much say like I want to
build XYZ, I want to build this and then
let's create some specifications for
this. So it would say the AI would start
to create a document. Okay, it product
needs to do this, it needs to do that,
it needs to do that, it needs to do
that, etc. And you would create this
this plan
um and the specifications. And then once
you had all of these documents
only then you would read those and you
would approve those and then only then
you would like go into uh development
mode and you would actually ask your
agents to start uh writing the code and
to start building the thing. That was
pretty much the meta um one year ago
when we just got these like big
breakthroughs with cloud code open 4.5
4.6 six, right? Like the good old glory
days of AI [laughter] AI agents. Um, and
now it's just like getting crazier and
crazier. So, um, the thing is there's
still value in that and I don't think
it's wrong to go through that process
even just to help you think about what
it is that you want. But the thing is
what I find myself doing most of the
time right now, I just like I go
straight into building and like I let
the model figure out what it like how it
should structure things. And there are
of course certain kind of like standards
that I kind of like steer the model
towards when I'm for example working
with the Python programming language
just because I've so much experience
with that. But like the summary of this
it gets easier and easier and easier to
just tell it what you want and it will
start to it will start to build it will
start to build it. So coming back to you
started this question. So let's say
people have this idea and what is the
next step? I would say right now get on
codeex, get on cloud code, use GPT6
Astra or Opus 5.5 which are currently
like two top frontier models. Opus 5.5
really good so far.
>> Super good.
>> Super good. And just tell it tell it
what you want to build.
>> And and the Yeah. And as as simple as it
sounds for people just starting out,
there's not much more to it. And then
you just look at the output and you tell
it what you like, what you don't like,
and that will already get you really,
really far.
>> Yeah. And and the cool thing about that
is that I think humans are really good
at explaining what they want. Like, you
know, it's easy to say, I want this, I
want this, but you really just have to
sort of go through that grill me process
where you have AI interview you about
>> what specifically do you want? What do
you not want? What does this look like?
What is your vision? And I was just
talking to a few Google engineers and
and they were explaining this as saying
like
>> the plumbing, the boring stuff on the
back end that that we used to have to
think about
>> where humans used to have to set that
all up before they could start to be
creative and think about the vision.
That plumbing is pretty much just taken
care of now because you explain what you
want and the agents know how to go set
up all that stuff so that you can really
just they kept calling it intent driven
automation or intent driven engineering
and I thought that was pretty cool. I
wanted to see do you agree with that? Do
you agree with that narrative or that
mindset?
>> Yeah, for sure. I I really like that. I
like that term intent driven. And um
what does it mean? You just tell the
model what you want. Like you you have a
certain intent as a builder, you have an
idea and you want to make that a
reality. And the thing is often
when you start with something even
though you might have like
a rough idea of where this thing should
go
until you actually see it in front of
you and use it. Um
you cannot really give the the best
feedback I found. So you can like then
that's why I've moved away from like big
plans and specs and all of that. just
like just just build me this and then I
see it and I look at it and I test it
and it's like hm this feels a little bit
off or can we make that faster or this
doesn't really look right like whether
whether it's visual or actual logic
right or the output here is wrong like
can we fix that right and um that's also
now the pretty much the like the
development process with glido the tool
that we're building right now it's
mostly like ideas and then just using
natural language like it's actually fun.
We're using glider to build glider,
right? So, we use glider to talk to it.
It's like, hey, can you try this, you
know, like let's build it out. And often
I do that straight on the um like
production codebase. I'll do it on a
separate branch, right? So, it's not
like immediately shipped, but like there
there's there's not even like a
playground. I just create a new branch
and it's like build it and then I can
directly see what it looks like in the
product itself and then I can iterate on
it. And then that's I think uh a perfect
description of like intent driven
development. You just tell it yeah
>> what what you want and it will build it.
>> By the way guys, I've got this
completely free SOP for you about
getting your first a automation client.
It's going to go over the exact steps
that has been proven for hundreds of our
AIS Plus members to get their first paid
gigs. It goes over the one sentence
service pitch that can get you started
today. Why your first client should cost
you money. The 5-minute video that
answers can this person actually deliver
before you've actually received any
money. what to do when you have zero
case studies. There's so many good
things in here that are going to help
you out. Even if you already do have
clients, I would recommend grabbing this
because like I said, it's yours
completely free. So, if you want to grab
this, there's a link for it down in the
description. Let's get back to the
video. That's so cool. It It's really
interesting how you kind of pointed out
how the meta a year ago was doing all
this kind of planning, but now you say
you're you're you're kind of building
first more and then really just getting
it in your hands and playing around with
it. I remember when I used to use plan
mode first for everything even not even
if I was building automation but I would
just use plan mode default just to sort
of brainstorm and it sounds like maybe
do you think the models are just getting
better and the models and harnesses are
getting better so that's why the med has
shifted or
>> yeah it's just and it's it's for sure
the combination so that's also important
to um to understand um and I think even
like people that are actively working on
clawed code on the development I think I
even saw this on X like entropic
engineers mentioning this as well that
plan mode is not even really needed
anymore because yes like models get
better but um it is essentially also
within the harness because what what
what is really a plan right it is first
>> essentially getting you give it you
always start with a goal or a task I
want to build this and then before it
would help the model to first plan out
so be before just getting into like uh
code generation
it would first like zoom out a little
bit. Okay, let's just first reason over
this like let's see if everything makes
sense and then once we have the plan I
can now execute on of it and it feels
like um the engineers working at OpenAI
and Tropic is essentially by making
those models and the harnesses better
and more capable they just merge this
process as like a trait that the model
and the harness combination already have
without like turning the plan mode on H
that makes sense. So now let's say we
have started to throw in some of the I
want statements and now we're getting
some stuff back.
>> Yeah.
>> In automation,
>> you know, we run a lot of evals and we
see, okay, cool. We have this, you know,
we have these inputs, we have these
outputs, this is, you know, 90% correct.
Let's make some iterations and and see
if we can get this to like 98 99. How do
you think about from a, you know, an app
perspective or a software perspective
essentially the eval process? What does
it look like to verify? What does it
look like to see if the things actually
work rather than just assuming it does
or having you, you know, go in there and
click through a few times?
>> Yeah. [snorts]
So,
this all this of course depends very
much on what you're uh building, of
course, because uh output quality. So,
what what does good look like is always
tied to the application that you're
building, right? So, let's
[clears throat] talk about glido. What
does good look like? Well, um, Glido
works well. If you press a button,
people can talk. That will be processed
in under 500 milliseconds and the text
will be pasted back into your
application like exactly the way you
wanted to see there, ready to paste
text. So, it will correct some errors
and all of that while leaving generally
most of your speech intact. Like that's
what people want from a dictation app.
So it starts with that getting clear on
what does good look like.
Then the second question is can we find
examples of that? Can we find examples
of cases uh where it went well? And in
glido for example uh we don't use user
data because we like really designed
this application to be private by design
but we use the data of uh uh our uh our
accounts internally meaning the
developers that work on glido right so
we use our own kind of like data sets
that we collect we have a bunch of
people so that data set then also grows
and in there we can run these
experiments so we have data sets in
there like when we put this into our
system we expect this to come out and
and that essentially then becomes
becomes an epha, right? Uh that you can
run and that you can check against.
>> Uh the cool thing is that as models and
harnesses get better and capable,
>> whenever you have some data and when you
don't have some data, you can even ask
the model to generate some realistic
data for your use case. And again,
whatever you're building, whether that's
a chatbot, an automation of any sort.
And once you give these models an
objective in terms of like here's what I
want this to look like. Here's what I
want you to improve on. I want it to be
faster. I want it to look more like
this. I want it to be better. I want to
have less errors. Once you give that and
let that run in a loop and that pretty
much means you tell it to go and improve
it. Use the data, generate more if
needed, do research, use sub agents, run
this in the loop until it gets better.
like it's a very messy prompt, but even
just saying giving that prompt to a
model like Opus 5.5 given the thing that
you're building will kick off this like
research experiment well where it will
go on it and we'll try to find ways to
to make it better. So what we find over
and over again is like the better models
and harnesses get, the easier all the
things that we have to do as developers
get. planning, spec different
development, quality assurance,
debugging, security, evaluations,
you know, all of these things also get
easier as the models get better. So, I
think that's a really interesting uh
property that that I found uh and also
just something that you need to be aware
of because you do need to ask the model,
right? So, you do need to be aware of
like what are Eiles? How can I set up a
loop in order to make my application
better? So just that realization
>> and asking [clears throat] it
>> is is the right starting point.
>> Yeah. So it sounds like
defining what does good look like and
that's something that you would do with
a human as well. You know, you're
setting the expectations of what do you
want? Because if you don't align with a
human or an agent on what you're looking
for, then when it comes back with
something that isn't aligned, it's maybe
not that it failed. Maybe it's just that
you didn't you weren't clear enough on
that. Yeah.
>> And then from there,
>> giving it a way to essentially verify
that, you know, whether that's you
verifying or or the agent verifying. I
think kind of a combination of both. But
>> what is good? Here's how you verify it.
>> And
um what you were saying about this whole
like loop, it made me think of when
Carpathy's like auto research came out.
And I think that's when I remember
having this big moment of like, wow,
like agents can actually
>> see their goal, prove it, and then keep
researching and keep trying again until
they hit it. And I thought that was
incredible. Now, I've got an interesting
one for you to kind of stem off that,
which is a lot of the best auto research
or goal prompts or loops are when you
have an objective milestone to make them
hit.
>> What about how do you think about it if
it's subjective? If it is something
that's more like taste or, you know, if
the definition of good isn't something
that can be objectively proven.
>> Yeah. Um, that's very true. Whenever you
have something that's very easy like
it's either good or bad but because you
have a data set with examples those are
the best scenarios or making things
faster right so for glido we also have a
lot of infrastructure that we need to
manage uh models that we deploy um and
there also code code and architecture
around that if you just give it an
objective like hey here's what we're at
right now in terms of latency you can
test that by running a test now go make
it faster
>> you know super clear because every time
it runs an iteration, it can see am I
above or below? Am I going to in the
right direction? So, what if you have a
use case that doesn't have this? And uh
let's think about an example of this to
uh make it a little bit more tangible.
So,
>> my most common is like video editing and
I want it to like I'm saying like yeah,
make it feel professional, make it feel
engaging. It's like how does it know?
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah. Yeah. So
like that that really is a tricky it's
really a tricky example. I I'll give you
one more and then I'll also consider
this one.
>> Okay.
>> Think about this. But um we have for
example also done a lot of work in
customer support in customer care. And
the thing is when a uh customer asks a
question and the AI agent gives it a
reply, right?
There are hundreds, thousands, probably
even like millions of different ways
that you could reply to a customer and
they could all be correct or they could
all be wrong because the final goal in
this case is that the customer is happy,
right? So like they got a good reply.
But whether you use a different word,
yes or no, that is all um subjective
meaning there can be there can be
differences. So one of the techniques
that you can use for that is what you
would call an LLM as a judge to run that
at scale because and how how does this
work right so like the um the best way
to to check the outputs of your AI
agents when it's subjective uh the best
way which is also the most expens
expensive and non-scalable way is you
you refle
the AI do the work a human refuses it
and says this is not good, this is good,
etc. But then what's the point of
automating it? Because in the case of
like customer care, if a human needs to
review every ticket, they could probably
just reply themselves, right? Because
it's probably easier to reply than to
review and give good comments. So that's
unscalable. But if you do that for a
little while, you could create a little
data set around it. when the uh customer
asked this and the AI said that the
human said this is good yes or no
because you know you start to collect
data and then this whole concept of an
LLM as a judge is you use another
language model so another like
independent language model call or
multiple calls or however you want to
set it up in order to review the output.
So you let an LLM look at the let's say
the reply to the customer and you let
the LLM say is this good yes or no and
why now the challenge is in the
beginning as you know like an LLM might
say yes this is good or no this is not
good but how but then how do you know
that is good right so you like shift the
problem from like an LLM that you need
to check to another so there's a little
trick for that and that is uh
essentially called creating alignment
between the human reviewer and the LLM.
And you can do that by let's say you
have 100 examples and you let the human
review 100 examples and you you list all
of this. You have an Excel spreadsheet
for this whatever. This is like manual
work. Nobody wants to do this. It's
unscalable. But you need to do this
because this is where you can
essentially capture the taste. So human
will say I like that. I don't like that.
That should be better. And now what you
want to do is you let an LLM run over
all of that and you see where they where
do they agree where do both the human
and the LLM say this is good and this is
bad and you'll get a score. So you'll
have a percentage. So let's say the
alignment is 80%. Or maybe maybe even
like 50%. So 50% of the time the LLM
agrees with the human yes or no. This is
baseline. And now once you have that
data this is where the interesting thing
comes in. Now you can use AI again. So
now you can say hey here's human data
here's LLM data let's optimize the
system prompt so we can create more
alignment you know now you can do loops
so then the LLM is a judge is it's a
system prompt and a model that's pretty
much it and then um if you let an LLM
review that like oh yeah I can see the
LM things a little bit different about
this and this and that and I thought
this was good but actually the human
thought this was not correct so I'll
change that in the system pro you run it
again alignment is at 75 5%. Cool. Let's
do another round. 80% 90% 95 99%.
And now if you have a large enough
sample size and you do this occasionally
to avoid model drift, you'll have an LLM
that with two degree of certainty agrees
with how a human would review it. That's
generally how it is done on real world
projects. Coming back to your video
editing example, you would follow a same
process,
but I would say it's probably even
trickier because assessing what good
looks like in an edit or an animation or
a cut, there are some things that are
obvious like some you can make an error,
but if like a title has like a certain
animation
pattern or something like that and you
don't really like that, that's tricky.
But it's mostly because of the LLM's
ability to inspect the visuals,
>> right? I think that's what makes it more
tricky. So, as multimodal capabilities
get better, you can apply this exact
same process even to optimizing and
training your video editing agents.
>> Mhm. Yeah. Yeah, I think the interesting
thing there too is like let's say you
have worked on refining this LLM as a
judge
>> and it's really really good
>> and then if you switch the model it
might not be as good anymore because the
model might interpret it differently.
But what's cool about that is you're
putting in that time which is a tedious
process because you're essentially
creating these standards but then you
can use sort of that loop that you know
auto research loop on it to have it
continuously optimized which I think is
>> very very cool
>> and
it's it makes me think of it makes me
think of like sports teams. They'll have
these scouts that will go out and watch,
you know, high school games or college
games or whatever it is. And there are
stats like height, weight, you know, how
many times can they bench press 225.
There's stats like that that are
objective. But then that's also like the
team trust the scouts opinion to say
this person has like this guy has
potential. He's explosive. He has great
game sense. Like that's stuff that you
can't pick up on paper as much. And it's
like how do you get your LLM to have the
taste and the judgment of that scout or
of you? You know what I mean? And I
think that that is
>> super super cool. Um, now as we
transition into
now we've been running some
verification, we have something that we
trust that's working. What if we want to
turn this from a oneperson app or a team
app, what if we really want to scale it?
Like what are the things that you start
thinking about? Um, and we don't have to
get super super technical, but what are
the high level things you start thinking
about around
infrastructure, databases, security,
that sort of things. And then if you
have any like examples of maybe
landmines that you've stepped on when
trying to scale something,
>> that'd be super interesting.
>> Yeah, let's dive into it. This is my uh
this is my fun zone pretty much.
[laughter] I like it. So um let's indeed
make it a little bit more like tact
tactical and therefore also technical
for the audience because up until this
point also my um recommendations for
people may have been quite obvious. Just
use cloud code, right? Just ask the
model, bro. And the funny thing is um
that's true. That's what you should do.
But there is still a part when you
really want to take things to the next
level where um it is very worthwhile to
like train yourself and to get a better
understanding of how software works. And
I keep coming down to describing that as
just the highlevel architecture
of your application and the software
that you're building.
And there are two distinctions between
that. And this is very worthwhile to
like research a little bit what I'm
about to say. So this could even be you
with like codeex with with cloud like
spend some time asking the the the
following terms that I'm going to
mention. So architecture first of all we
have it at uh what I call the system
level. And this means how do all of the
individual components like your back
end, your front end, and your database
and potentially even other services, how
do they talk together? Because most
software products
are a combination of those things,
right? And it's very it's very important
to understand what the role is of each
and every one of those how they
communicate to each other and what are
some of like the traits the unique
things and also the things that you need
to care about when it comes to those
individual things. Right? So this
depends heavily on first of all what are
you building? Are you building a web
application, a desktop application, a
mobile application? uh something that
combines all of those. So it depends. It
also depends on what language do you
use. Do you for example use languages
where you have a very clear separation
between your back end let's say that is
built in Python for example or in Rust
or in C and do you have a front-end
application so the visual layer that is
maybe in JavaScript you're using Nex.js
JS. So then you have usually like
completely different code bases. Now you
can also have projects that for example
just work in one stack. So you do
everything in TypeScript for example. So
TypeScript that whole project it is your
back end and it is also your um like
your front end your visual component to
that. So those are all things that
matter based on what you're building. So
now that you get a little bit more
serious, that is a good like first
question to ask your AI agents. Hey, I'm
building XYC.
What would be the best stack? And then
stack is the important word here. What
would be the best stack in order to
build this? Do I need a separate back
end and a front end? What kind of
database should I use? Can I put
everything together? So those are then
questions that you can go through and it
will give you examples and you can just
ask like hey what does that mean? What's
the simplest solution? what fits the
best for kind of like what I'm building
and because that is a really important
starting range because once you log in
on a on a programming language like
within the language itself you can do a
lot right you can scale up you can scale
down you can refactor you can build but
switching a project to a different
language even though with coding agent
it becomes easier and easier and easier
that is usually not a trade that you
that you want to make right we had to do
it with glido at some point um it was a
lot of like we started out on a
different stack than what we use right
now because in the beginning we didn't
do our research properly. It was also a
little bit because of team structure. We
had someone working on that and the
other one working on that and then we
decided to go in a direction and then
later we figured out
>> um we need to do this differently. So
that's that's a landmine that uh that I
that that we stepped on. it was choosing
the kind of like things we're we're
familiar with rather than picking uh the
tool or the stack that was really like
most optimized for what we eventually
wanted to build. And in the past
um this would pretty much have not been
possible. So if you are comfortable with
a with a stack, you've been developing
that for 10 years, you most likely want
to use that, right? But I think that now
changes. You could now very well say,
"I'm confident with that stack, but
there is there's evidence there's
actually evidence that this stack is way
better for what we're trying to do.
Let's let's go with that stack." So,
architecture at the system level,
backend, front end, database, how does
everything talk to each other? Then you
also have architecture at like the
project level. So, this is when you go
inside, let's say, your GitHub
repository and how you structure your
projects in there. This is less
important than the higher level system
architecture, but it's still important
to have like a rough understanding of
how do you structure projects in terms
of files and folders. So, what do you
put in there? And how do you structure
your code in terms of functions,
classes, and modules that you create? So
when you're creating code and these
agents get better at it every month, but
you can still have these like spaghetti
code bases. You know, you build
something here, then you build something
there, then you build something there.
And this uh can happen quite quickly
when you are vibe coding and you go from
idea to idea to idea and you experiment
a lot, which is a new way of building,
right? You just ask it to build
something and it might build something.
Now you have this artifact in there.
>> Then you decide, let's leave it there. I
don't really like it. let's come back to
it later. You build something else. You
forget about it, you know. So now you
have this mess. You have this junk
sitting in there and that might have
>> some logic in there which you still
really use and which you still really
need, but it's got all of this bloat
around it that was just a test feature
that you wanted to build. Now you start
to build on top of that and you create
these new features. It's all great, but
they still depend on this kind of like
messy little part that's really deep way
into your codebase. So this is how you
get spaghetti code codebase, right? So
over time it gets harder for your AI
agents to manage and to find where where
everything is. And this is where you
you'll run into bugs at scale. So all of
a sudden things stop working, right? It
it worked fine for 3 months and then all
of a sudden
>> things don't work anymore. And it's
because you removed the feature that was
>> not no longer needed, but it contained a
little part that you actually still
needed. So
>> understanding how that works at a high
level is
>> very valuable to do. And I'm going to
give people like one tip to look into.
There's a really good skill for this and
it's called um I think it was recently
changed but it's from Matt BCO. So this
is like he's famous for his skills,
right?
>> Great engineering skills.
>> Yeah, great great engineering skills.
So, it used to be called improve
codebased architecture, but I think he
refactored that a little bit to I think
codebased design or something like that.
But if you
>> we'll find it, we'll link it in the
description.
>> Yeah, if you search for Matt PCO and
then find some of his skills where he
talks about uh improving architecture
about how to create deep modules and
locality and how to work with with the
seams. That is a skill that I very often
uh use to review my code bases and that
uh he even like mentioned that he
created that skill to fight AI slop and
make code bases that are easier to
navigate by AI
>> and imagine how cool that really is
where I just said pretty much there
there's two components that I still are
that are still I think very high
leverage to learn more about
architecture at like the system level
and the codebase level. For the codebase
level, there's literally just a skill
that you can use. And if you just read
that skill and use it in your coding
agents, you'll get better at it.
>> To me, that's just amazing that that's
how you get how you get better at it.
And then the and then the the like the
front end database back end,
>> spend a day re researching that.
>> Like if you're serious serious about
building stuff, just like ask questions.
like even do it on like lunch break, go
out, take a walk, like start to learn a
little bit about what that means, how
they communicate to each other and also
what the different um security aspects
are of those different levels because
security applies to like your entire
application. But there are specific
things that your database handles u your
back end handles, your front end handles
and the communication layers between
those.
>> Mh. [clears throat]
Yeah, I think it's really cool that you
brought up the skills of Matt PCO
because one of the things that I was
thinking about as you were going off
there was what you mentioned at the
beginning which which was that the fact
that really under the hood software
engineering is still the same but the
human role has changed
>> because of the fact that these things
are so smart and can move so fast but
still the principles of building good
code are still the principles of
building good code. And for someone like
me or for a lot of people probably
watching this, maybe when you started
saying like Python, C, Rust, they were
like, "What are those things?" You know,
but that's been around for so long. And
people like Matt PCO, people like you
know what it looks like to have a good
codebase. And that means that you can
leverage the subject matter expertise
and experience of other people if you
ask the right questions, if you have it
do research, if you leverage skills like
that. And I think that that part is
really cool and hopefully gives people a
lot of a lot more comfort in in the fact
that they're not alone in building this
app because there's so much stuff out
there from people that understand what
what does good look like when maybe you
can't define good as well as someone
else can, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> So, the last piece I wanted to touch on
then is I know you hit on a little bit,
but
what should people be thinking about
when it comes to the security stuff like
not only from like a data privacy but
also how do you think about
what's the potential of your app getting
hacked you know that sort of thing too
how do you think about that especially
if you have no background in any sort of
like cyber security
>> sort of stuff
>> so the cool thing about this is that
with
um very little uh like ju with just the
the basics you can go really are. So, of
course, security is this big domain and
there's different levels to it, but I
also don't come from like a security
background. I wouldn't even consider
myself a security expert. Uh we do have
yours on our team who knows way more
about that and I've picked up most of
the things from him uh over the years.
But like I've said, the cool thing is
there are actually like if you do a hand
uh a handful few things, you already are
it's almost already impossible for you
to get hacked. So let me give you a
couple of those things to look into and
there is a little bit of overlap between
like what we would call infrastructure.
So that is the whole concept of okay we
talked about architecture at like the
system level backend front end database
right infrastructure pretty much means
like where do all of those services live
where are they deployed and how do they
talk to each other and what are for
example the firewalls around them
there's a little bit of overlap in there
and again um very um high lever thing
that you can look into even if it's just
like from a research curiosity
perspective ive to learn more about
this. So let me walk you through some
examples to make this a little bit more
tangible. So
let's start with like a database. For
most people building something, you want
a database, right? Most applications
need a database. You need to store user
accounts, passwords, any information
that you might need in your database.
And right now the most popular option
for that is Superbase. Superbase is a
really popular database. And Superbase
is amazing. If I would say to anyone, if
you don't have a very strong reason to
not use uh Superbase, use Superbase.
Meaning that if you're nontechnical, if
you're just starting out, just use
Superbase. It is flexible enough that
you can do anything with it. Don't be
like uh bothered by people saying, "Oh,
you really need like an unstructured
database for this use case," or like,
"Oh, you need a dedicated factor
database." Like Superbase can do all of
that. Just use that. And then like I've
said, if you have a very strong argument
as to why you don't like Superbase, then
you're probably technical enough to make
the decision on your if you get what I
mean, right? So
>> that makes sense. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So database, use Superbase.
>> So Superbase
um it's you can also self-host that by
the way, but for most people I would
recommend just use it in the cloud. That
means go to superbase.com, create an
account, create a database. There you
can get on a uh a plan and you have your
database. Now then what I recommend to
do is again spend a couple of hours
talking about the security aspects and
best practices that you can set up
around Superbase. Superbase is great out
of the box. But there are some things
you need to be aware of. This mostly has
to do with rowle security. Again I'm
just putting out these terms in here not
to go into them but for people to like
research into that. So rowle security is
important. like look up what that means,
how you can work with that. Uh make sure
that your database has like a strong
password, like common sense, strong
password. Make sure that your user
account that you can log into on
Superbase, strong password and also
potentially two-factor authentication.
This is all very simple stuff, right?
But this is just avoiding like people
and random bots being able to like
randomly guess a password and can get
into something. Now then also, so that's
your database. So now your data lives in
there. If you use Superbase in the
cloud, you put on rowle security and you
have strong passwords and you make sure
that all your services that connect to
it use the credentials in like
environment variables without like
actually putting it into into code,
you're already in a good spot. There's
more that we can do, but this is already
from a database perspective a good
start. Now then when it comes to your uh
back end which is the second most
important thing because for your back
end usually you have data flowing right
so your front end application
um may load data directly from your your
database or it can also go uh through
your back end right so your back end
talks to your database and then your
back end like uh uh puts that uh or like
flows that data through to your front
end. So the back end is another part
where you need to be aware of first of
all like what language do you use and
then second where do you deploy that? So
where does that code live? So when you
start building something it's on your
laptop it's local host. You're running
things you're testing things but when
you deploy something you actually put it
in the cloud and this is where people
can get access to it. So there are of
course various a lot of different
services that you can use. You have
tools like Railway and Render that make
it really easy one-click deployment. Um,
you can rent a virtual private server.
You can use Azure, AWS, GCP. So,
different types of ways that you can set
this up.
Um but the most important thing is that
when you deploy your back end that you
set up ideally some type of firewall
rule around this where you restrict
certain traffic to it and this is again
something that you just need to do some
research in depending on which platform
do you use which language do you also
use uh and then use your AI coding
agents to talk about okay what is like a
firewall how can I set that up now this
also applies applies to your your
database and you can do this in the
superbase uh dashboard. But why this is
important is usually there is a part of
your application that is userfacing.
That's typically your front end meaning
that's the that's what people actually
see. They go into the browser or in a
desktop application and they use that
and then your back end and your database
no one should be able to touch that.
only your user application is you should
be able to pull information from that
and uh your front- end application is
then also deployed somewhere again can
be any of the services that you use
maybe you use it on for sale uh the
thing is that deployment there uses an
IP address so that is a specific address
from which it reaches out to either your
database or to your back end and I know
it gets a little bit technical but
Firewall pretty much means you set up a
rule where you say in your back end and
in your database
only open the door if the request is
coming from the IP address that I
whitelisted which is my known front end
or desktop application. And now there is
very different rules depending on how
you set up your like your infrastructure
and how you set up your architecture and
your applications. But that is the like
general uh best practices around
security. Setting up the proper
firewalls and then making sure secrets,
API keys, credentials, all of that are
handled correctly. So you cannot read
them in your application code. people
cannot read them uh by for example in a
web application inspecting the code in
the browser right so if you protect your
secrets and your credentials you have
rowle security on and you put proper
firewalls on your database your back end
and whitelist it for your like front end
application that is security in a
nutshell and again it's technical but
it's more so for people like to take
this snippet summarize it put it
[clears throat] into like a chat and
then reason through this what that means
for your application
Yeah, I love that. That was a master
class. And I think one of the things
that
>> have become very clear throughout this
conversation with different technical
concepts that you've brought up is that
a lot of this sounds like it's just
about awareness. If you can bring up
this conversation to your agent and let
it go do the thinking and the
understanding of
>> implementing,
>> but you were the one who had to say,
"Hey, think about this and do this."
Right. I think that's very cool.
>> Yeah. It's it's those unknowns unknowns
that you in the beginning as a new
builder developer need to become aware
of so that you can ask the right
questions to your AI agents. It's not
about the skills or even the
intelligence or uh the years of
training. It's just the awareness being
able to like ask the right questions and
then also with the base level
understanding that you have being able
to somewhat reason over those answers
right where you can say yeah that is
important and let's not get into this
right now because those are not kind of
like the basics that goes way deeper
that's not important for my application
right now at this stage
>> I love it let's let's wrap up here with
with one final sort of like
big statement from you what I want to
hear from you is
basically I want you to start the
sentence like this. If I was starting
today with no technical experience, I
would be most excited about this. Like
what is the opportunity and what gets
you excited like thinking about the
future of where AI is headed and what
you're able to do with it in this, you
know, software engineering or building
apps sort of space.
>> Cool. That's the I really like this. So,
um, yeah, here's I would answer. So, if
I were just starting out and I see what
what's going on around me with all of
this technology,
what I would be most excited about is
the opportunities
it can create for each and every one of
us. So I out of university
quite randomly happened to land on a
freelance gig and worked self-employed
pretty much ever since then. Started to
build businesses off of that and that
has given me insane amounts of freedom
and getting to work on exciting things
that I want to build. And I think that
is now within reach for more and more
people because of this gigantic
transformation that we as the world will
be going through in this AI
transformation.
And you might be thinking, yeah be when
the tools get easier, everyone can do
this. True, but we still need
implementers. We still need builders.
The fact that it is possible and that we
can do it doesn't mean that everyone and
every business will actually take the
initiative to start to start doing this,
right? So there are just going to be so
much opportunities
to for like pretty much um
entrepreneurial things to build things
on your own to to sell that to make that
available to make content to help local
businesses or maybe not even local but
to help larger businesses to be able to
be excited about the technology about
the automation about the transformation
and then getting better at that craft as
you do it and then being able to like
monetize off of that. And if that is
exciting to people watching, which I
know it probably is because I know your
audience, right? Then I would say like
go go all in on that. And if you even if
you're not just starting out, but you
may already have a job, like figure out
how you can do this on the side, right?
Um, I for example have an entire
community of freelance developers and
data professionals and I also share that
with people because the opportunities
are real. You can do this next to a
full-time job. You can pick up a project
and while you're doing your day job, you
can just kick off another agent and let
it do the work, right? You can even use
your phone to talk to Claude on lunch
break. Give it a master prompt and when
you're back home like it has built the
automation for your client. So I would
say that's the most exciting thing. Um I
recently watched a podcast uh it was on
Lex Fritman and we had DHH the I don't
even like it's David blah blah blah. DHH
is is is what he goes by online
typically. And he described it as having
a genie in a bottle. Like we as
developers now have a genie in a bottle.
I like that.
>> Meaning that you can just think about it
>> and you can prompt it into existence.
>> And you're not even limited to three
wishes. You can just keep asking.
>> You're not you're just limited
[laughter] to your tokens.
>> Yeah. That's that's what you got to be
careful
>> to your weekly token budget. Yeah. Yeah.
But I think that is that that is a great
like description and you know this as
well Nate because I see all of these
videos from you when whenever every time
a new model releases like the stuff that
they can do just gets crazier and
crazier and crazier and it used to be on
like this yearly timeline where if you
looked one year back like the models
were like extremely way way better. I
think now we have it already like on a
quarterly basis where you have these
like really holy this is so much
better than what we had right and that
will that will continue I I don't see a
world where that is going to stop
>> so you just need to learn how to like
use these tools and then build stuff
with it and then use that to ultimately
create the life that you want because
like building stuff just for the sake of
it is fun but I It's a we have a great
opportunity to like help yourself, help
your family, and to create a life around
these tools that was just not possible
years ago.
>> Mhm. Yeah. I think the the only way we
see the the progress slow down is if
this whole like pacing the frontier
discussion that's going on right now, if
there's an actual standard in place for
regulation and for
>> I guess kind of like a a national and
global coordination. So, we'll see what
happens there. But
>> there go f They go f steam hats. There's
no stuff.
>> Oh man, we could do we could probably do
a whole another hour talking about this
stuff. I think it's really interesting
as well. But
>> um this space has been, you know, so
exciting, so fun. I'm so glad that I've
been able to connect with people like
you and hang out in person and just, you
know, you're super smart guy. So I
appreciate you coming on. This has been
a super informational
episode. So really appreciate you coming
on. Dave, where can people get in touch
with you or learn more from you if
they're interested?
>> Cool. Appreciate it, Nate. Uh, just go
to my YouTube channel, Dave Ablar.
Mostly
videos for a more technical audience.
But that said, what does that matter
nowadays? Like I make sure that my
tutorials, I also create these kind of
like handbook guides for them nowadays
because it's so easy. I used to just
create tutorials and teach them. Now I
create a tutorial and I just say to AI
like create a whole entire documentation
page for it so people can walk through
it step by step. So the cool thing is I
mostly do kind of like big builds how to
build this. For example, I just launched
a video how to build an entire company
knowledge base and then actually do it
properly like something not just like
the toy project but actually something
that you could like offer to a company
and it's for a technical audience but
you could also just use your AI agent
and point it at the GitHub repository in
the handbook and it can build it for
you. So yeah, YouTube Dave Ablar that's
where you find me.
>> Sweet. I love it. Well, thanks so much
for hopping on today Dave and maybe we
can do it again sometime.
My pleasure, Nate. Talk soon.
>> Awesome. All right. See you, Dave.